hmtweb.com 2018-03-10

# G-Squared Interactive Privacy Policy | Internet Marketing Driver

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for G-Squared Interactive ** ** and our website; https://www.gsqi.com **.** This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:

  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

**Cookies  
**We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Advertising**  
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing services and Facebook advertising to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors of our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using a contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search engine results page (SERP), on a site in the Google Display Network, or on Facebook and/or Instagram. Third-party vendors, including Google and Facebook, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to gsqi.com. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with Google’s privacy policy, and Facebook’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/). You can learn how to [adjust Facebook’s privacy settings](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217) to control how ads are targeted to you based on your activity off of Facebook.
